Guide to the Music Department Records: Series 3, Concert Programs, 1863-[ongoing]
Music Department Records: Series 3, Concert Programs, 1863-[ongoing]
- Series 3. Concert Programs, 1878-[ongoing]
  - General Concerts
    - December 8, 1984: Wesleyan University Orchestra, performed by Wesleyan University Orchestra, Roger Solie (Box 4)
    - December 9, 1984: Candlelight Concert, performed by Wesleyan University Concert Choir, Recorder Ensemble, Virginia Hancock (Box 4)
    - December 11, 1984: A Memorial Service, performed by Bill Roberts, Karl, Scheibe, Talitha (Box 4)
    - January 25, 1985: Piano Recital: Charles Hansen, performed by Charles Hansen (Box 4)
    - January 30, 1985: Charles Krigbaum, Organist, performed by Charles Krigbaum (Box 4)
    - February 1-3, 1985: Wesrevue III, performed by The Wesleyan Singers, Virginia Hancock, et al. (Box 4)
    - February 7-8, 1985: Moliere's The Imaginary Invalid, performed by Scott H. Schneider (Box 4)
    - February 15, 1985: Jorg Demus: Piano, performed by Jorg Demus (Box 4)
    - February 20, 1985: John Noel Roberts, Piano, performed by John Noel Roberts (Box 4)
    - February 21, 1985: Music from Czechoslavakia, performed by The New Word Consort of Wesleyan University, Roger Solie (Box 4)
    - February 24, 1985: Violin Recital: Peter Winograd, performed by Peter Winograd, Rohan DeSilva (Box 4)
    - February 26, 1985: Contents Under Pressure, performed by Various (Box 4)
    - March 2, 1985: An Afternoon Chamber Recital: Music for Flute and Harpsichord, performed by Maura Kelly, Britt Wheeler (Box 4)
    - March 5, 1985: Wesleyan University Orchestra, performed by Wesleyan University Orchestra, Roger Solie (Box 4)
    - March 29, 1985: Afro-American Music, performed by Bill Barron, Bill Lowe, Ed Blackwell, Wes Brown, Fred Simmons (Box 4)
    - April 1, 1985: George Russel Will Give a Lecture on His Lydian Chromatic Concept of Tonal Organization for Improvisation, performed by George Russel (Box 4)
    - April 5, 1985: Friday Noon Recital Recital Series, performed by Ann O'Hanlon, Jennifer Brandon, Gabrielle Mason, Alison Valtin (Box 4)
    - April 12, 1985: The Friday Lunchtime Recital Series, performed by Hildreth Wilson, Doug Neuman (Box 4)
    - April 12, 1985: Wesleyan University Big Band, performed by Wesleyan University Big Band, Bill Barron (Box 4)
    - April 19, 1985: Frans Brueggen, Transverse Flute and Recorder; John Gibbons, Harpsichord, performed by Frans Brueggen, John Gibbons (Box 4)
    - April 20, 1985: South Indian Classical Music, performed by T. Viswanathan, David Nelson, Marcie Frishman (Box 4)
    - April 26, 1985: A Day of World Music in Honor of Jon B. Higgins, performed by Various (Box 4)
    - April 26, 1985: South Indian Music, performed by T. Viswanathan, Trichy Sankaran (Box 4)
    - April 27, 1985: Doug Newman, Piano, performed by Doug Neuman (Box 4)
    - April 30, 1985: Kevin Wimmer: Honors Thesis Recital, performed by Kevin Wimmer (Box 4)
    - May 1, 1985: Britt Wheeler, Organist, performed by Britt Wheeler (Box 4)
    - May 3, 1985: A Friday Lunchtime Recital Series, performed by Rima Muth, Tony Lutkins, Michael Taylor, Elizabeth Connell (Box 4)
    - May 3-5, 1985: A Festival of Birthdays, performed by Wesleyan University Concert Choir, Wesleyan Singers, Wesleyan University Orchestra (Box 4)
    - May 10-11, 1985: Spring Dance Concert, performed by Various (Box 4)
    - May 10 and 17, 1985: Javanese Music and Dance, performed by The Wesleyan Gamelan Ensemble, Sumarsam, I. M. Harjito, Suratno, Urip Sri Maeny (Box 4)
    - May 17, 1985: Machinal, performed by Sandy Cohen, et al. (Box 4)
    - September 14, 1985: Afro-American Music, performed by Bill Barron, Bill Lowe, Fred Simmons, Ed Blackwell, Wes Brown, Tony Purrone (Box 4)
    - September 20, 1985: New World Consort, performed by Peter Standaart, Roy Wiseman, et al. (Box 4)
    - October 3-5, 1985: The Dining Room, performed by Annie Ravitz, et al. (Box 4)
    - October 11, 1985: Katsuya Yokoyama: An Evening of Shakuhachi Music, performed by Katsuya Yokoyama, Susumu Miyashita, Bertil Chikudo Petersson (Box 4)
    - October 18-20, 1985: Carly Churchill's Cloud 9, performed by Chris Ryan, et al. (Box 4)
    - October 23, 1985: Philip Prince, Organist, performed by Philip Prince (Box 4)
    - October 25, 1985: Anner Bylsma: Violoncello and Violoncello Piccolo, performed by Anner Bylsma (Box 4)
    - October 26, 1985: A Program of Music by Ludwig van Beethoven, performed by Various (Box 4)
    - November 1, 1985: Experimental Music, performed by Ron Kuivila, Alvin Lucier, Meredith Monk, Thomas Ridenour (Box 4)
    - November 2, 1985: French & American Music for Flute and Piano, performed by Peter Standaart, William Braun, et al. (Box 4)
    - November 6, 1985: Musical Groupings, performed by Various (Box 4)
    - November 8, 1985: A Friday Noon Lunchtime Recital Series, performed by Elizabeth Connell, Lisa Cerbone, Rima Muth (Box 4)
    - November 8, 1985: The Borodin Trio, performed by Rostislav Dubinsky, Luba Edlina, Yuli Turovsky (Box 4)
    - November 8-10, 1985: The Trojan Women, performed by Clay Stevenson, et al. (Box 4)
    - November 15, 1985: Nineteenth-Century Sacred Music, performed by The Concert Choir, Robert Ford, et al. (Box 4)
    - November 22, 1985: A Friday Noon Lunchtime Recital Series, performed by Jennifer Brandon, Doug Neuman, Gabrielle Mason (Box 4)
    - November 22-24, 1985: Twelfth Night, performed by Ernest Lafky (Box 4)
    - November 23, 1985: The Wesleyan Singers, performed by The Wesleyan Singers, Robert Ford, et al. (Box 4)
    - November 24, 1985: The Wesleyan Women's Choir, performed by The Wesleyan Women's Choir, Robert Ford, et al. (Box 4)
    - Undated: The Maids, performed by Cobina Gillitt, M. Robinson, K. Pratt, E. Greene, et al. (Box 4)
    - Undated: What the Butler Saw, performed by Grant Fairlie, et al. (Box 4)
    - Undated: The Persecution and Assassination of Jean-Paul Marat as Performed by the Inmates of the Asylum of Cherenton under the Direction of the Marquis de Sade, performed by Julia Lee Barclay (Box 4)
    - December ?, 1985: My Sister in This House, performed by Daisy von Scherler, et al. (Box 4)
    - December 4, 1985: Festival of India, performed by Various (Box 4)
    - December 6, 1985: West African Music and Dance, performed by Abraham K. Adzinyah, Freeman K. Donkor, Maxwell Amoh, et al. (Box 4)
    - December 6 and 8, 1985: French Christmas Music, performed by The Wesleyan Singers, Robert Ford, et al. (Box 4)
    - December 7, 1985: The Wesleyan University Orchestra Performs Mozart's Concerto for Flute and Harp, K. 299, and Other Works, performed by The Wesleyan University Orchestra, Melvin Strauss, Peter Standaart, Sally Ranti, et al. (Box 4)
    - December 11, 1985: Charles Krigbaum, Organist, performed by Charles Krigbaum (Box 4)
    - December 12, 1985: Holiday Concert, performed by The Ebony Singers, The Jubilee Singer, Charles Garner, et al. (Box 4)
    - December 12-15, 1985: Winter Dance Concert, performed by Pierre Hecker, et al. (Box 4)
    - January 24, 1986: Vocal Recital, performed by Martha King, Neely Bruce, Patricia Harper (Box 4)
    - January 26, 1986: Contemporary Music Concert, performed by Rebecca Bower, Martin Kluger (Box 4)
    - January 31, 1986: Delphin and Romain, performed by Wilfred Delphin and Edward Romain (Box 4)
    - February 1, 1986: A Recital of Music for Oboe and Piano, performed by Caesar Thomas Storlazzi, Sarah Meneely-Kyder (Box 4)
    - February 7, 1986: Celtic Wind Music and Dance, performed by Nancy Crutcher, Jim Cowdery, Connie Powell, Lauren Cowdery (Box 4)
    - February 8, 1986: Faculty Ensemble: African-American Music, performed by Bill Barron, Bill Lowe, Ed Blackwell, Wes Brown, Fred Simmons (Box 4)
    - February 14-16, 1986: Wesrevue IV, performed by Wesleyan Singers, Robert Ford, Karen Escovitz, et al. (Box 4)
    - February 18, 1986: Patricia Snyder, Organist, performed by Patricia Snyder (Box 4)
    - February 21, 1986: The New World Consort, performed by The New World Consort (Box 4)
    - February 22, 1986: CCI: Black Composers' Concert, performed by Wesleyan University Big Band, Wesleyan University Ebony Singers, The Wesleyan Singers (Box 4)
    - February 23, 1986: Music Through the Light: A Concert in Memory of Timothy R. Alcock, performed by Various (Box 4)
    - February 28, 1986: "Hartford," "Northampton" & "Saybrook", performed by The American Music/Theatre Group, The New World Consort, Neely Bruce, et al. (Box 4)
    - March 2, 1986: Piano Music, performed by Donald Berman, David Feldman (Box 4)
    - April 2, 1986: All-Connecticut Composers Concert, performed by Sharon Derby, Randall Gordon, Edward Diemente, Sarah Meneely-Kyder, Gwyneth Walker, Neely Bruce (Box 4)
    - April 4, 1986: The Concert Choir and The Wesleyan Singers, performed by The Concert Choir, The Wesleyan Singers, Robert Ford (Box 4)
    - April 4, 1986: A Friday Lunchtime Recital Series, performed by Kerry Rosenthal, Thom Lissey, Dawn Norfleet, Ann O'Hanlon (Box 4)
    - April 13, 1986: A Concert Javanese Music, performed by Various (Box 4)
    - April 16, 1986: Sanda Schuldman and William Braun: Duo-Pianists, performed by Sanda Schuldman, William Braun (Box 4)
    - April 18, 1986: The Wesleyan University Big Band, performed by The Wesleyan University Big Band, Bill Barron, et al. (Box 4)
    - April 22, 1986: James Welch, Organist, performed by James Welch (Box 4)
    - April 25, 1986: South Indian Music, performed by T. Viswanathan, Trichy Sankaran (Box 4)
    - April 28, 1986: Ebony Singers, performed by Ebony Singers, Charles Garner (Box 4)
    - May 3, 1986: Wesleyan Orchestra & Wesleyan Concert Choir, performed by Wesleyan Orchestra, Melvin Strauss, Wesleyan Concert Choir, Robert Ford (Box 4)
    - May 4, 1986: Folk and Art Songs of the Jewish People, performed by Leon Lishner, Melvin Strauss (Box 4)
    - May 7, 1986: Real People: Music by Paul Austerlitz, Performed by "The People", performed by Paul Austerlitz, "The People" (Box 4)
    - May 9, 1986: Javanese Music, performed by The Javanese Dance/Gamelan Ensemble. Sumarsam, I. Harjito and Maeny (Box 4)
    - May 10, 1986: Choral Music by Twentieth-Century American Composers, performed by The Wesleyan Singers, Robert Ford, et al. (Box 4)
    - May 11, 1986: The Sacred and the Profane, performed by Susan Garber, Connecticut Valley Harmony (Box 4)
    - Undated: Blood Drum Spirit, performed by Various (Box 4)
    - September 12, 1986: Copasetics, performed by The Copasetics (Box 5)
    - September 18, 1986: A Concert of South Indian Music, performed by T. Viswanathan, Trichy Sankaran (Box 5)
    - September 20, 1986: Lakshmi, Bharata Natyam Dancer, performed by Lakshmi, T. Viswanathan, David Nelson, Josepha Cormack, Matther Allen (Box 5)
    - September 26, 1986: Afro-American Music, performed by Bill Barron, Bill Lowe, Fred Simmons, Ed Blackwell, Wes Brown (Box 5)
    - October 4, 1986: East Encounters West, performed by Margaret Leng Tan (Box 5)
    - October 9-11, 1986: Distant Fires, performed by David X. Greene, et al. (Box 5)
    - October 10, 1986: Nexus, performed by Bob Becker, Bill Cahn, Robin Engelman, Russ Hartenberger, John Wyre (Box 5)
    - October 13, 1986: Alexander String Quartet, performed by Eric Pritchard, Kate Ransom, Paul Yarbrough, Sandy Wilson (Box 5)
    - October 17, 1986: Experimental Music, performed by Ron Kuivila, Alvin Lucier, Philip Glass (Box 5)
    - October 17-19, 1986: La Ronde, performed by Amanda Marks, et al. (Box 5)
    - October 29, 1986: Philip Prince, Organist, performed by Philip Prince (Box 5)
    - November 1, 1986: Romantic Music, performed by Melvin Strauss, Robert Ford, Doug Neuman, Risa Renae Harman, Korby Myrick, Martin Thompson, Gary Crow-Willard (Box 5)
    - November 2, 1986: French and American Works for Violin and Piano, performed by Paul Woodiel, Neely Bruce (Box 5)
    - November 6-8, 1986: Mass Appeal, performed by David Milch, et al. (Box 5)
    - Undated: The Telephone; Trouble in Tahiti, performed by David Nafisian, Thomas Lissey, et al. (Box 5)
    - Undated: The Lion in Winter, performed by David G. Stevens (Box 5)
    - November 6, 7, and 12, 1986: Djerdan: The Tufts Balkan Ensemble, performed by Djerdan (Box 5)
    - November 8, 1986: Music from the English Manor House, performed by Robert Ford, et al. (Box 5)
    - November 9, 1986: Chamber Music Recital, performed by William Braun, Sharon Dennison, Peter Standaart (Box 5)
    - November 11, 1986: The Apsara Dance Ensemble, performed by Sam-Ang Sam (Box 5)
    - November 14, 1986: Wesleyan University Big Band, performed by Bill Barron, Bill Lowe (Box 5)
    - November 19, 1986: Ronald Ebrecht: Organist, performed by Ronald Ebrecht (Box 5)
    - November 21, 1986: Wesleyan Chamber Ensemble, performed by Roy Wiseman (Box 5)
    - December 5, 1986: Igor Kipnis: Harpsichord, performed by Igor Kipnis (Box 5)
    - December 6, 1986: Igor Kipnis Playing the Harpsichord and Fortepiano with the Wesleyan University Orchestra, performed by Melvin Strauss, Robert Ford, Doug Neuman, Risa Renae Harman, Korby Myrick, Martin Thompson, Gary Crow-Willard (Box 5)
    - December 7, 1986: Annual Candlelight Concert, performed by Wesleyan Concert Choir, Wesleyan's Chorus, Robert Ford (Box 5)
    - December 8, 1986: The Ebony Singers Holiday Concert, performed by The Ebony Singers, Charles Garner, Joy Lambe (Box 5)
    - December 12, 1986: Top of the Lizst, performed by Various (Box 5)
    - December 12-13, 1986: Dances, performed by David Milch, et al. (Box 5)
    - January 23, 1987: Neely Bruce and Christopher Oldfather, Duo-Pianists, performed by Neely Bruce, Christopher Oldfather (Box 5)
    - January 24, 1987: Horn Recital, performed by Kaitlin Mahony, Jennifer Tao (Box 5)
    - January 30, 1987: The New World Consort, performed by Lynn Crigler, Roy Wiseman, et al. (Box 5)
    - February 1, 1987: A Dripping Honeycomb, performed by Barbara Lachman Grant, Marie Pintauro Nakouzi, Willa Cooper Needler, Ellen Tamm Sweeny (Box 5)
    - February 3, 1987: Music of the Ottoman Court and the Turkish Dervish Brotherhoods, performed by Ihsan Ozgen, et al. (Box 5)
    - February 5-7, 1987: Dracula, performed by Annie Ravitz, et al. (Box 5)
    - February 6, 1987: African-American Music, performed by Bill Barron, Bill Lowe, Fred Simmons, Ed Blackwell, Wes Brown (Box 5)
    - February 7-8, 1987: Wes Revue, performed by Karl Slovin, et al. (Box 5)
    - February 11, 1987: Paul Orgel, Piano; Christopher Costanza, 'Cello, performed by Paul Orgel, Christopher Costanza (Box 5)
    - February 15, 1987: Piano Recital, performed by Virginia Eskin (Box 5)
    - February 17, 1987: The Apsara Dance Ensemble, performed by Sam-Ang Sam, et al. (Box 5)
    - February 20, 1987: Celtic Wind Music, Dance, and Song, performed by Nancy Crutcher, Jim Cowdery, Connie Powell, Lauren Cowdery (Box 5)
    - Undated: An Evening of Orchestral Premiers, performed by Bill Lowe, et al. (Box 5)
    - February 27, 1987: Ensemble Chanterelle, performed by Sally Sanford, Catherine Liddell, Kevin Mason, Peter Becker, Olav Chris Henriksen (Box 5)
    - February 28, 1987: Music from the Court of the Sun King, performed by The Wesleyan Singers, Robert Ford, et al. (Box 5)
    - March 28, 1987: Flute: A Senior Thesis Concert, performed by Matthew Reid-Schwartz (Box 5)
    - April 2-4, 1987: Alice Through the Looking Glass, performed by Grisha Coleman, Jeremy Dobrish (Box 5)
    - April 3, 1987: Wesleyan University Big Band, performed by Wesleyan Big Band, Bill Barron (Box 5)
    - April 3-4, 1987: Gestuary, performed by Susan Foster, Ron Kuivila, et al. (Box 5)
    - March 25, 1987: Charles Krigbaum: Organist, performed by Charles Krigbaum (Box 5)
    - April 10, 1987: Music of South India, performed by T. Viswanathan, Trichy Sankaran, Matthew Allen (Box 5)
    - April 11, 1987: Wesleyan Women's Chorus and Concert Choir, performed by Women's Chorus, Concert Choir, Robert Ford (Box 5)
    - April 13-14, 1987: L'Avare, performed by Nancy Griffin, et al. (Box 5)
    - April 15, 1987: Gordon Monahan, performed by Gordon Monahan (Box 5)
    - Undated: An Aberration: Not Just Any Fashion Show, performed by Michele Barnwell (Box 5)
    - April 22, 1987: George Barth, Fortepiano; Janet Packer, Baroque Violin, performed by George Barth, Janet Packer (Box 5)
    - April 24, 1987: Music for Two Elizabeths, performed by The Wesleyan Singers, Concert Chior, Robert Ford, et al. (Box 5)
    - May 2, 1987: The Wesleyan University Orchestra, performed by The Wesleyan University Orchestra, Melvin Strauss (Box 5)
    - Undated: Ebony Singers' Spring Concert - 1987, performed by Ebony Singers, et al. (Box 5)
    - May 8, 1987: Wayang Kulit, performed by Sumarsam, I. M. Harjito, et al. (Box 5)
    - May 16, 1987: The Spring Dance Concert, performed by Various (Box 5)
    - September 18, 1987: Strings and Percussion: A Concert of South Indian Traditional Music, performed by Geetha Bennett, Frank Bennet (Box 5)
    - September 19, 1987: The Kathak Ensemble, performed by Janaki Patrik, Paul Leake, Brad Catler, Marjorie Johnson, Steven Gorn (Box 5)
    - September 24, 1987: Robert Taub, Pianist, performed by Robert Taub (Box 5)
    - October 7, 1987: Greatest Hits Concert, performed by The Wesleyan Singers, Robert Ford, et al. (Box 5)
    - October 7, 1987: James Dalton: Organist of Queen's College, Oxford, performed by James Dalton (Box 5)
    - October 9, 1987: Faculty Concert, performed by William Braun, Julie Charland-Ribchinsky, Sharon Dennison Parry, Sally Ranti, Peter Standaart (Box 5)
    - October 15-17, 1987: The Importance of Being Earnest, performed by Thomas Quaintnace, et al. (Box 5)
    - October 16, 1987: Igor Stravinsky: Mass; Arthur Honegger: King David, performed by CONCORA, Richard Coffey, Hartford Chamber Orchestra (Box 5)
    - October 17, 1987: Goro Yamaguchi: Music for Shakuhachi, performed by Hozumi Yamaguchi, Chizumi Kimura, Ralph Samuelson (Box 5)
    - October 29-31, 1987: Originale, performed by Karl Slovin, Roderick Murray, et al. (Box 5)
    - October 30, 1987: The American Music/Theatre Group, performed by Neely Bruce, et al. (Box 5)
    - October 30-November 1, 1987: Signs † Wonders: A New Musical, performed by William Francisco, Carl Goodman, Kit Reed, et al. (Box 5)
    - November 1, 1987: Sophia Bilides: Greek Folk Music Ensemble, performed by Sophia Bilides, David Bilides, Stephen Mock, Jane Hemenway (Box 5)
    - November 5, 1987: Ross Aiken Gortner, Jr., performed by Various (Box 5)
    - November 6-7, 1987: The Wesleyan University Orchestra & The Wesleyan Concert Choir, performed by The Wesleyan University Orchestra, Melvin Strauss, The Wesleyan Concert Choir, Robert Ford, Korby Myrick (Box 5)
    - November 10, 1987: New Sounds-Technologies-Ideas, performed by Robert Black (Box 5)
    - November 13, 1987: In the Spirit of John Coltrane, performed by Ed Blackwell, Fred Simmons, Wes Brown, Bill Lowe, Kamau Adilifu, Andrew White (Box 5)
    - November 19, 1987: Kronos Quartet, performed by David Harrington, John Sherba, Hank Dutt, Joan Jeanrenaud, Joseph Celli (Box 5)
    - November 20, 1987: English Choral Music, performed by The Wesleyan Singers, Robert Ford (Box 5)
    - November 21, 1987: Bharata Natyam: A Concert of South Indian Classical Dance, performed by Kay Poursine (Box 5)
    - December 4, 1987: Liederabend, performed by Ann Monoyios, James Richman (Box 5)
    - December 5, 1987: The Wesleyan University Orchestra, performed by The Wesleyan University Orchestra, Melvin Strauss, Ann Monoyios, et al. (Box 5)
    - December 5, 1987: Bring Your Own Sofa Party, performed by Hillary, Paul, Julie (Box 5)
    - December 6, 1987: The Wesleyan Women's Chorus, performed by The Wesleyan Women's Chorus, Robert Ford, et al. (Box 5)
    - December 7, 1987: Ebony Singers' Winter Concert, performed by Ebony Singers, Marichal Monts (Box 5)
    - December 11, 1987: West African Drumming and Dance, performed by Abraham K. Adzenyah, Freeman K. Donkor (Box 5)
    - December 11, 1987: Annual Candlelight Concert, performed by The Concert Choir, Robert Ford, Arnold Thomas (Box 5)
    - December 12, 1987: Concert of Javanese Gamelan Music and Dance, performed by Wesleyan Gamelan Ensemble, I. M. Harjito, Sumarsam, Urip Sri Maeny (Box 5)
    - December 11-12, 1987: Pandemonium, performed by Various (Box 5)
    - Undated: 1987 Premiere: Wesleyan Student Filmmakers, performed by Various (Box 5)
    - January 22, 1988: Voice Recital: Peter Hart, performed by Peter Hart, Neely Bruce (Box 5)
    - January 27, 1988: Charles Krigbaum: Organist, performed by Charles Krigbaum (Box 5)
    - February 5-6, 1988: Wesrevue, performed by Various (Box 5)
    - February 11-13, 1988: $100,000 Reward!: J.W.B vs. The Wholes, performed by James Childs, Neely Bruce, Kathleen White, et al. (Box 5)
    - February 12, 1988: African-American Music, performed by Bill Barron, Bill Lowe, Fred Simmons, Ed Blackwell, Wes Brown (Box 5)
    - Febraury 19, 1988: New World Consort, performed by New World Consort, Roy Wiseman, Britt Wheeler, Sharon Dennison, Peter Standaart (Box 5)
    - February 22-27 1988: John Cage at Wesleyan, performed by Various (Box 5)
    - March 4, 1988: An Evening of Mozart, performed by The Wesleyan Singers and the Concert Choir, Robert Ford (Box 5)
    - March 5, 1988: Yerma, performed by Karl Sikkenga (Box 5)
    - Undated: Jayaprana; a Balinese Love Story, performed by I Nyoman Saumandhi, Fredrik E. deBoer, et al. (Box 5)
    - Undated: Friends, performed by Jonah Pesner, et al. (Box 5)
    - March 5, 1988: Orchestre de l'Université Wesleyan, performed by Wesleyan University Orchestra, Melvin Strauss (Box 5)
    - March 6, 1988: All-American 20th Century Sonata Program, performed by William Cerny (Box 5)
    - March 9, 1988: David Arcus, Organist, performed by David Arcus (Box 5)
    - March 27, 1988: A Choral Presentation by the Wesleyan Singers, performed by The Wesleyan Singers, Robert Ford (Box 5)
    - April 8, 1988: Experimental Music, performed by Alvin Lucier, Steve Reich, New World Consort (Box 5)
    - April 9, 1988: Urban Bush Women, performed by Jawole Willa Jo Zollar, Pamela DeCarlo, et al. (Box 5)
    - April 13, 1988: New England String Quartet, performed by Elenn Jewett, Heidi Lee Yenney, Holly Barnes Morrison, Kris Yvon Yenney, Paul Orgel (Box 5)
    - Undated: Worthless Music, performed by Mladen Milicevic, et al. (Box 5)
    - April 15, 1988: Two Days in Memory of T. Ranganathan, performed by T. Viswanathan, Trichy Sankaran, Ramnad Raghavan, Lakshmi, Harjito, Sumarsam (Box 5)
    - April 16, 1988: Wesleyan University Big Band, performed by Wesleyan University Big Band, Bill Barron (Box 5)
    - April 21-23, 1988: Small Craft Warnings, performed by Alexandria Aron, et al. (Box 5)
    - April 27, 1988: Blood Drum Spirit, performed by Paul Hadzima, Brett Anderson, et al. (Box 5)
    - April 30, 1988: A Concert of Early Music, performed by The Wesleyan Choral Groups, Robert Ford (Box 5)
    - May 2, 1988: Ebony Singers' Spring Concert, performed by Ebony Singers (Box 5)
    - May 5-7, 1988: Usonian Houses, performed by Karl Slovin, Carl Goodman, et al. (Box 5)
    - May 7, 1988: Wesleyan University Orchestra, performed by Wesleyan University Orchestra, Melvin Strauss (Box 5)
    - September 15, 1988: Navaratri 1988: A Concert of South Indian Music, performed by T. Viswanathan, W. Thyagarajan, Ramnad Raghavan, David Nelson (Box 5)
    - September 17, 1988: Bharata Natyam: A Concert of South Indian Classical Dance, performed by Lakshmi, G. Balaji, Jody Cormack, Matthew Allen, T. Viswanathan, Douglas Knight (Box 5)
    - September 23, 1988: Early Music for Organ, performed by Robert Ford, The Wesleyan Singers (Box 5)
    - September 24, 1988: Flute and Piano Recital, performed by Peter Standaart, William Braun (Box 5)